# Abraham Yang

# Frontend Web Developer



I am a software engineer and frontend web developer speciallizing in the Javascript and css, familiarizing with React framework and Material UI library. I build successful websites and web apps that are fast, easy to use, and coded with the same eye for detail as a designer, and have abundance of experience on minisite for automobiles, meetings and devices.

#### **PERSONAL**

+86 159-2109-8538



abram.yang@outlook.com



Minhang, Shanghai, China



Mandarin Chinese, English

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript(ES6)



React.js

MaterialUI

Photoshop

**MJML** 

EDM )



jQuery

Webpack )



NodeJS

Handlebar.js

Vue.js

# **EDUCATION**

## Shanghai Dianji University

# **Electronic Engineering**

Bachelor's degree 2019

#### Certificates:

College English Test Brand 4 (CET4) College English Test Brand 6 (CET6) College Computer Rank Level 2

Web Design of CITT Level 3

Scholarships: Level 2 -x2 / Level 3 -x5

#### **HOBBIES**







Gaming



Photography

Calligraphy

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

# Software Enginner @ Publicissapient, Shanghai

### Huawei Honor Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

The minisite made by React framework and Material UI library post the race about the microsoft 365 user to create excellent subjects and let them upload their works to backend to earn a reward.

#### IQOS EDM:

Build eDM template to implement on salesforce CRM by Mjml eDM framework.

#### DS Automobile:

Collaborate with my team to build a fast, fade animated, artistic and responsive website.

#### Huawei MWC2020 Minisite

Follow the design of UI/UX designers to build a faster, animated and functional website. This website is used for display the video and news of the Live, and be able to filter the video by tags.

#### Huawei History Minisite:

This website is only for landscape view, whatever users rotate the phone would show the same view, and shown as a storyline to users for telling the history of Huawei.

#### Huawei MBBF Minisite template:

This website is used for display the video and news of the MBBF, and show the location of the exhibition.

#### SAICMotor Roewe&MG:

Maintain the official website and build vehicle pages periodically.

#### Software Enginner Intern @ Publicissapient, Shanghai 2019.04 - 2019.07

#### Marriott CN official website

I participated in the Marriott CN Locale Project with Indian team. Baidu Map development implement on Marriott, read the the documentation and write English document for introduction for wechat JSSDK.







wechat: abramyangcn



github.com/abramyangcn



twitter.com/abramyangcn

# **Project Details**

# Software Enginner @ Publicissapient, Shanghai

2019.07 - NOW

#### Huawei Honor Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

The minisite made by React framework and Material UI library post the race about the microsoft 365 user to create excellent subjects and let them upload their works to backend to earn a reward.

#### IQOS EDM:

Build eDM template to implement on salesforce CRM by Mjml eDM framework.

#### DS Automobile:

Collaborate with my team to build a fast, fade animated, artistic and responsive website.

#### Huawei MWC2020 Minisite

Follow the design of UI/UX designers to build a faster, animated and functional website. This website is used for display the video and news of the Live, and be able to filter the video by tags.

#### Huawei History Minisite:

This website is only for landscape view, whatever users rotate the phone would show the same view, and shown as a storyline to users for telling the history of Huawei.

#### Huawei MBBF Minisite template:

This website is used for display the video and news of the MBBF, and show the location of the exhibition.

#### SAICMotor Roewe&MG:

Maintain the official website and build vehicle pages periodically.

#### Marriott CN officail website

During this experience, I participated in the Marriott CN Locale Project with Indian team.

Basically, the component which contains baidumap and the Wechat share of proof of concept was assigned to me, and I attended the voice meetingand sent 2 e-mails every day to report my progress for better coordinate.

Baidu Map development on Marriott: read the documentation of Backbone.js and handlebars.js to develop, Features below:

Focus on hotel card to pin the hotel marker

Customize the info window cloned from hotel card

Customize the cluster and its info window

Show the duplicate hotel marker

Click the marker to show popup.

Wechat JS-SDK:

Read the the documentation and write English document for introduction.









# 杨杨 Abraham Yang

# 前端开发工程师



Abraham是一名软件工程师和前端web开发人员,擅长Javascript和css,熟悉React框架和Material UI库。主要建立网站和网页应用程序,这些网站和应用程序速度快,易于使用,编码时对细节有着与设计师相同的眼光。在汽车行业、会议和移动设备的网站上有丰富的经验。

# 个人信息

+86 159-2109-8538

 $\searrow$ 

abram.yang@outlook.com

▦

中国 上海市 闵行区



普通话,英语

## 技能

Javascript(ES6)

Sass

React.js

MaterialUI

Photoshop

MJML

EDM

GatsbyJS

jQuery

Webpack

Gulp

NodeJS

Handlebar.js

Vue.js

## 毕业院校

### 上海电机学院

电子信息工程

本科 2019

证书:

全国大学英语4级(CET4)

全国大学英语6级(CET6)

上海市计算机2级

网页设计3级职业技能证书

奖学金: 二等奖 --x2 / 三等奖 --x5

#### 兴趣爱好







游戏

X±;

**福影** 



-

# 工作经验

# 前端开发软件工程师 @ 阳狮集团Publicissapient,上海2019.07 -至今

华为荣耀 Minisite: Microsoft365 challenge

此页面使用了React框架以及Material UI库,全球用户可以上传自己的作品来参加创作比赛,荣耀的后台审核完毕之后公布获奖者。

## IQOS EDM 邮件营销:

与日本、新加坡以及印度团队协作,使用了MJML框架来写edm的模版,在salesforce marketing cloud 上部署。

#### 法国 DS 汽车:

在团队协作下完成了DS汽车官网的开发,页面非常迅速,法式艺术以及响应式。

#### 华为世界移动通信大会大会 MWC2020 Minisite:

遵循UI/UX设计师的设计,构建一个更快、更生动、更具功能性的网站。这个网站用于展示示现场的视频和新闻,并能够通过标签过滤视频。

#### 华为历史 Minisite:

本网站仅为横向浏览,无论用户旋转手机,都会显示相同的视图,并以故事情节向用户 展示华为的历史。

华为全球移动宽带论坛 MBBF Minisite template:

该网站用于展示MBBF的视频和新闻,并显示展位的位置。

#### 上汽集团荣威&名爵:

维护官方网站,定期上新车辆页面。

# 软件工程师实习 @ 阳狮集团Publicissapient,上海 2019.04 - 2019.07

#### 万豪集团中国官方网站

I participated in the Marriott CN Locale Project with Indian team. Baidu Map development implement on Marriott, read the the documentation and write English document for introduction for wechat JSSDK.







wechat: abramyangcn



github.com/abramyangcn



twitter.com/abramyangcn